WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-02-13-1981-02-16; WJZ-EVMAG-079-016 (Mixed materials 79, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-02-13; WJZ-EVMAG-079-017 (Mixed materials 79, Tape 17)
    - Chesapeake Ice Boating, 1981-02-13; 1 (Mixed materials 79, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-02-27-1981-03-05; WJZ-EVMAG-080-001 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-02; WJZ-EVMAG-080-002 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 2)
    - Orioles Off Season, 1981-03-02; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-03; WJZ-EVMAG-080-003 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 3)
    - Happy Birthday Twinkie, 1981-03-03; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-03-1981-03-04; WJZ-EVMAG-080-004 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-04; WJZ-EVMAG-080-005 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 5)
    - Behind the Scenes of P.A.T., 1981-03-04; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-04-1981-03-10; WJZ-EVMAG-080-006 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-05-1981-03-06; WJZ-EVMAG-080-007 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-5; WJZ-EVMAG-080-008 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 8)
    - Maryland's Snow Mobile Champ, 1981-03-05; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-09; WJZ-EVMAG-080-009 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 9)
    - Worlds Sexiest Designer, 1981-03-09; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-09; WJZ-EVMAG-080-010 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 10)
    - Ads That Seduce You, 1981-03-09; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-10; WJZ-EVMAG-080-011 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 11)
    - I'll Break Your Clutter Proble, 1981-03-10; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-11; WJZ-EVMAG-080-012 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 12)
    - The Al Jolson of Highlandtown, 1981-03-11; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-11-1981-03-16; WJZ-EVMAG-080-013 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-11-1981-03-12; WJZ-EVMAG-080-014 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-13; WJZ-EVMAG-080-015 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 15)
    - Special Olympics Hockey, 1981-03-13; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-14; WJZ-EVMAG-080-016 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 16)
    - W.W. Star, 1981-03-14; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1981-03-16; WJZ-EVMAG-080-017 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 17)
    - Blast Hometown Star, 1981-03-16; 1 (Mixed materials 80, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-01-26-1984-01-27; WJZ-EVMAG-093-001 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 1)
    - Florida's Bikini King, Chef Tell: Cheese Scuffle, Stress Testing For Cops, Beneath The Lincoln Memorial, Weekend Guide, Venice-California Video., 1984-01-26; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 1)
    - The American Jimmy Conners, Dating Coach, How Sophisticated Are You?, Space Age Back Rock, Video Postcard, Sinbad-A Real Sailor, 1984-01-27; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-01-1984-02-02; WJZ-EVMAG-093-002 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 2)
    - TV's Vixens, Playgirls' Man of The Year, Harvey Illustrates, Hidden Costs, Waterskiing On Your Palms., 1984-02-01; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 2)
    - J.R. And Mom Firedivers, Weekend Guide-SPH, Cat Rock Painter, Buddy Holly Rocks On., 1984-02-02; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-03-1984-02-06; WJZ-EVMAG-093-003 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 3)
    - Fashion For Passion, Marriage Theater, Dumpees, Baltimore- A Portrait, Bob Scarlette: The New Coffee Blitz., 1984-02-03; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 3)
    - "Face" Of The A-Team, Marilyn Beck, Olympic Ice Couple, Finding The Olympic Village, Socializing For Success., 1984-02-06; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Reel 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-093-004 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 4)
    - Video Mix, 1984-02-04; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-07-1984-02-08; WJZ-EVMAG-093-005 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 5)
    - Michael Jackson, Phenomenon, Rumbles Surfing Dog, Bob Barker-The Price Is Right, Buffalo George-Chairs, TV Covers Olympics., 1984-02-07; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 5)
    - Nude TV Commercials, San Diego Fights For ―Simon & Simon‖, Volcano Adventure, How Psychic Are You?, 1984-02-08; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-09-1984-02-13; WJZ-EVMAG-093-006 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 6)
    - Chris Atkins & Linda Grey's Dallas, The Real Silkwood Story, Chinese Violin Tech, All Beatles All The Time., 1984-02-09-1984-02-13; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-13-1984-02-15; WJZ-EVMAG-093-007 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-15; WJZ-EVMAG-093-008 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 8)
    - Mr. T Explosion, Hollywood, Photographer, B Scarlette: Yuppie, Jump Aerobics, James Brown., 1984-02-15; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-27-1984-02-28; WJZ-EVMAG-093-009 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 9)
    - The Other Side OF Midnight, Marilyn Beck, Ron Gallea, Exercising In Mind, 2.000 A Day Hotel Suite., 1984-02-27; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 9)
    - What Your Roman Fantasies Mean, Dirty Dancer, Jim Ralph, Gourmet Popcorn, 1984-02-28; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-02-29-1984-03-01; WJZ-EVMAG-093-010 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 10)
    - Newman's son-Robby Benson, Chicken Leash law, Prescription Fashion, Tom McMullen, Scarleatte: 3 Stooges., 1984-02-29; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 10)
    - Stay At Home Moms, Moonlighting Stars, Bob Lacy: Key west, Sandra Pinckney, Kung-fu Dare Devil, 1984-03-01; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-02-1984-03-05; WJZ-EVMAG-093-011 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 11)
    - Atypical Male Model, Ultimate Dance Challenge, Futuristic Homes, Pyramid Mystery Solved., 1984-03-02; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 11)
    - Legendary Kim Novak, Marilyn Beck, Dare To Be Dull, Town Adopts A Baby., 1984-03-05; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-06-1984-03-07; WJZ-EVMAG-093-012 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 12)
    - Dressing Joan And Linda, Rock ̳n' Roll Housewives, Baltimore Inventers, Country Doc Refuses Promotion., 1984-03-06; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 12)
    - Return Of ―Cagney & Lacy‖, Video Postcard, Chocoholics, Bob Callahan-Quiz, Heaviest Couple., 1984-03-07; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-08; WJZ-EVMAG-093-013 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 13)
    - Weekend Guide, 1984-03-08; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-08-1984-03-09; WJZ-EVMAG-093-014 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 14)
    - Dream Come True Kid, Dancin' Man, Bodyguard School, SPH-Weekend Guide., 1984-03-08; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 14)
    - Buffalo Man, My Life As A Man, Camp Beverly Hill, Bob Sarlatte, California Fashions., 1984-03-09; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-03-12-1984-03-13; WJZ-EVMAG-093-015 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 15)
    - I Survived, Update For ―Crash‖ Story, Paul Newman, Marilyn Beck, Dirty Work., 1984-03-12; 1 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 15)
    - Amazing Acrobatics Skiers, ―Trading Places‖ For Real, Dirt Scott, My Little Hero., 1984-03-13; 2 (Mixed materials 93, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-20-1984-04-23; WJZ-EVMAG-095-001 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 1)
    - The Almost Miss America, Grafitti Artists, Puppet Man, Chocolate Monks., 1984-04-20; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 1)
    - Coal Mining Rescue, Marilyn Beck, Hat Maker, Winvale: An Old Race, Buffalo George: Computer., 1984-04-23; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-24-1984-04-25; WJZ-EVMAG-095-002 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 2)
    - Ace's Painted House, Robert Pante, Melissa Grows Up, Faster Than A Speeding Bullet., 1984-04-24; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 2)
    - Jayne Kennedy Unlimited, Body Guard, Ragtime Shoeshine, Palm Springs, Callahan – License Plates., 1984-04-25; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-26-1984-04-27; WJZ-EVMAG-095-003 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 3)
    - Lion Tamer's Nightmare, Arnold's Little Brother, Maverick Movie Mogul, Weekend Guide., 1984-04-26; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 3)
    - Doing Double Duty, Space Shuttle Photographer, Bob Sarlatte, Old Bay., 1984-04-27; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-04-30-1984-05-01; WJZ-EVMAG-095-004 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 4)
    - Jamaican River, Marilyn Beck, Art Of Muppets, Olympic Judo, Snake Catchers., 1984-04-30; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 4)
    - Swimwear, Scorecard, Mary Decker: Olympic Sweetheart, World's Fastest Food, Shear Madness., 1984-05-01; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-02-1984-05-03; WJZ-EVMAG-095-005 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 5)
    - Rick Simon Revealed, TV's Funniest Pitchman, Hollywood's Practical Joke: "This Is Spinal Tap", Super Spa., 1984-05-02; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 5)
    - Aliens, La Cage Aux Follies, Michael Jackson's Dance Director, Weekend Guide, 1984-05-03; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-10-1984-05-11; WJZ-EVMAG-095-006 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 6)
    - Stefanie, Anthony Quinn's Secret Love, Sandra Pickney, Bob Guccione., 1984-05-10; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 6)
    - Fire Power, Marilyn Beck, So You Want To Be A Clown, Buffalo George, Mother's Day, Ballooning, 1984-05-11; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-14-1984-05-15; WJZ-EVMAG-095-007 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 7)
    - Where The Boys Are, Michael Jackson-Gary Indiana, Michael Jackson- After Gary Indiana, Battling Buddies., 1984-05-14; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 7)
    - Where The Girls Are, Muhammad Ali, Tan-Thru Swim Suits, Hotel Dominique., 1984-05-15; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-16-1984-05-17; WJZ-EVMAG-095-008 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 8)
    - Where The Stars Are, Danny Devito, Water Toys, Olympic Gold Getters., 1984-05-16; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 8)
    - 20 Minute Workout, Jack Parts Company, Cruise Capitol Of The World, Bob Sarlatte: Baby Photographers., 1984-05-17; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-18-1984-05-21; WJZ-EVMAG-095-009 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 9)
    - New York's Night People, Elvis The Doll, Conquering My Fear To Fly, Sandra Herbert's Weekend Guide, Fire Fighters., 1984-05-18; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 9)
    - Indiana Jones's New Lady, Chain Saw Smuggler, Marilyn Beck, Barbie Is 25!, 1984-05-21; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-23-1984-05-24; WJZ-EVMAG-095-010 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 10)
    - Ted Koppel, Break Dancing Success Story, Home Bodies Workout, Bob Sarlatte: Clowns Of The 80's, 1984-05-23; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 10)
    - Ron Howard, Miss America, Shirley Muldowney, Weekend Guide, Cabbage Patch Mink Coats., 1984-05-24; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-25-1984-05-28; WJZ-EVMAG-095-011 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 11)
    - Michael Douglas (Donna's), Diving For Gold, Shari- Belafonte Harper, Buffalo George: Beepers., 1984-05-25; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 11)
    - Shirley Speaks Up, Michael Jackson Look-A-Like Contest, Olympic Family, Light Star., 1984-05-28; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-05-29-1984-05-30; WJZ-EVMAG-095-012 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 12)
    - Howard Cossell, Cheryl Ladd, Billion Dollar Gem Collector, Buffalo Geo: After Graduation., 1984-05-29; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 12)
    - Spock Lives, Sky-High Rents, Dundalk Girls, Las Vegas Cigarette Girls., 1984-05-30; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-01-1984-06-04; WJZ-EVMAG-095-013 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 13)
    - A Legend Turns 20, Bill Graham-Rock Mogul, Manwatchers, Mermaid's Gate At The World's Fair., 1984-06-01; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 13)
    - The "Mouth" Star Of Police Academy, Paris In Baltimore, Amazing Indoor Flying, Buffalo George: Wedding., 1984-06-04; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-05-1984-06-06; WJZ-EVMAG-095-014 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 14)
    - Bedroom Photographer, Fly Me, Marilyn Beck, Olympic Chic Pt. 1, Bob Sarlatte: Baseball., 1984-06-05; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 14)
    - Michael Douglas (Donna's), Hollywood's Hot Copter Pilot, Message In A Bottle, Olympic Chic Pt.2, Rocky Roller Rink., 1984-06-06; 2 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-06-07; WJZ-EVMAG-095-015 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 15)
    - Shirley Caesar, 1984-06-07; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1984-07-07; WJZ-EVMAG-095-016 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 16)
    - Rev. A Green/RFK, 1984-07-07; 1 (Mixed materials 95, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-107-001 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 1)
    - I Have 18 Kids, Sailplane Adventure, Cabbie School, Meet The Elite., 1985-07-19; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-07-30-1985-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-107-002 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 2)
    - Rafting Through Alaska's Icebergs, Chic Junk Jewelry, Texas Oil Baron., 1985-07-30; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 2)
    - Life Of A London Bobbie, Secret Life Of Baseball, 50's Diner Pad, V.J. Day Remembered., 1985-07-31; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-01-1985-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-107-003 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 3)
    - New Life For Liza, Superman Diving Champ, Most Unlikely Beauty Queen., 1985-08-01; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 3)
    - On The Road With Bob Hope, Make-up Secrets Of The Stars, From Jail To Broadway, V.J. Day Remembered., 1985-08-02; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-05-1985-08-06; WJZ-EVMAG-107-004 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 4)
    - What's Next For John Pitter, Secrets Of Staying Young, Gliding Into Yosemite., 1985-08-05; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 4)
    - Dial A Prom, MD's Canoe Champs, Hottest Las Vegas Gossip., 1985-08-06; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-07-1985-08-08; WJZ-EVMAG-107-005 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 5)
    - We Sell Bizarre Beauty, Dept. Store Dynasty, Secrets Of The White House Barber, Bob Johnson Club., 1985-08-07; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 5)
    - Behind The Scenes Of "Live Aid", Baltimore's Bad Boys Of The Airwaves, Baby Penguins., 1985-08-08; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-09-1985-08-12; WJZ-EVMAG-107-006 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 6)
    - This Is Tom Jones; WE Blow Up Buildings, Dunbar Twin Superstars., 1985-08-09; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 6)
    - Bill Cosby's Private Life, Hard Hat Hunks, Rapping With The Fat Boys., 1985-08-12; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-13-1985-08-14; WJZ-EVMAG-107-007 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 7)
    - King Of Brat Pack, Magic Aid, Miss Wheelchair America., 1985-08-13; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 7)
    - Personal Side Of Kathrin Ross, What Would You Do For A New Car??, Baltimore's Part Time Strippers., 1985-08-14; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-15-1985-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-107-008 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 8)
    - Meet Mick Jagger's Girl, Night Court's Bull, High Steel Heroes., 1985-08-15; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 8)
    - Billionaire Hotel Queen, Royal Imposter, Post Time At The Pig Races., 1985-08-16; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-19-1985-08-20; WJZ-EVMAG-107-009 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 9)
    - Amazing Kreskin, Madonna Style, Regency., 1985-08-19; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 9)
    - Mutlley The Scuba Dog, Dennis Hooper's Back, Washington's Funnyside., 1985-08-20; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-23-1985-08-26; WJZ-EVMAG-107-011 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 11)
    - Secrets Of Disney Animation, King Of The Golden Arches, Clues From The Grave., 1985-08-23; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 11)
    - Diving For Gold, New Life For Jamie, We Are The World, Look Alikes., 1985-08-26; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-27-1985-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-107-012 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 12)
    - North Beach Leather, Harry Chapin Remembered, Baseball's Oldest Pitcher., 1985-08-27; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 12)
    - The Tallest Funnyman, Firewalking Craze, Petite Stunt Skier., 1985-08-28; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-27; WJZ-EVMAG-107-013 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 13)
    - Seduction Of Sports, 1985-08-27; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-29-1985-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-107-014 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 14)
    - Anne Baxter, Sailing Fastest New Boats, The Best Steamed Crabs, Harvard's Half-Time Havoc., 1985-08-29; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 14)
    - Olympic Love Story, Youngest Presidential Candidate, California Cave Crawling., 1985-08-30; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-09-02-1985-09-03; WJZ-EVMAG-107-014 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 15)
    - 75 Years Of Jacque Cousteau, Man Watchers Club, Natalie Cole., 1985-09-02; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 15)
    - Gene Hackman, Models Of Milan, Miss Tall International, Pink Flamingo's., 1985-09-03; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1985-08-21-1985-08-22; WJZ-EVMAG-107-010 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 10)
    - Joe Piscopo, Atlantic's Undersea Treasure, Brazilian Jungle, Music, Big And Wolfe., 1985-08-21; 1 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 10)
    - Emmanuel Lewis, You Can Be A Floozie, Tiny Taste Testers, Gnomes., 1985-08-22; 2 (Mixed materials 107, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-02-1988-05-06; WJZ-EVMAG-144-001 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 1)
    - Smell., 1988-05-03; 2 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 1)
    - Sound., 1988-05-02; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 1)
    - Taste., 1988-05-04; 3 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 1)
    - Touch., 1988-05-06; 5 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 1)
    - Sight., 1988-05-05; 4 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-04-1988-05-05; WJZ-EVMAG-144-002 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 2)
    - Sensations!-Sight, Meltdown Medic, The Ogopogo Monster, Chainsaw Masterpieces., 1988-05-05; 2 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 2)
    - The Town Of Many Wives, Sensations!-Taste, Centerfold Shuttlerbug., 1988-05-04; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-06-1988-05-09; WJZ-EVMAG-144-003 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 3)
    - The Girls Of Elite, Precision Parachute Team, George Carling Meets Mickey Mouse., 1988-05-09; 2 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 3)
    - Sensations!-Touch, Richard Chamberlain-Bourne Again, Celebrity Moms, Rough Riders., 1988-05-06; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-10-1988-05-11; WJZ-EVMAG-144-005 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 5)
    - Hollywood Lies, Deadly Scorpio Hunter, Atop The Big Apple., 1988-05-10; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 5)
    - Jay Leno Drives Them Crazy, Mob Buster, Florida's Flashy Covergirls., 1988-05-11; 2 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-11; WJZ-EVMAG-144-006 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 6)
    - Surrogate, 1988-05-11; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-12-1988-05-13; WJZ-EVMAG-144-007 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 7)
    - Hong Kong Overview, Hong Kong Action Movies, Ghosts Of Cathy, Hong Kong Nightlife., 1988-05-13; 2 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 7)
    - Inside US Magazine, Navy Commando Camp, Miami Bound Machine., 1988-05-12; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-05-13; WJZ-EVMAG-144-008 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 8)
    - 24 Hours In Baltimore, 1985-05-13; 1 (Mixed materials 144, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-147-001 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 1)
    - Tank Of Gas – Deep Creek Lake., 1988-07-06; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-08-1988-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-147-002 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 2)
    - Princess Grace & The Mob, Street Corner Symphony, Lady Di's Buys., 1988-07-08; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 2)
    - The Brothers Stallone, Mayor Sonny Bono, Hot Heads., 1988-07-11; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-12-1988-07-15; WJZ-EVMAG-147-003 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 3)
    - Revealing Calvin Klein., 1988-07-12; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 3)
    - Tank Of Gas – Atlantic City., 1988-07-13; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 3)
    - King Of The Night., 1988-07-14; 3 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 3)
    - Racing Roulette (High Power Outboard Racing)., 1988-07-15; 4 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-12-1988-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-147-004 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 4)
    - Revealing Calvin Klein, Unsung All-Star, Meg Ryan's Hot Streak., 1988-07-12; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 4)
    - Heavenly Loni, Outlaw Martin Sheen, Tank Of Gas Getaway Atlantic City NJ. Fly With The Wind., 1988-07-13; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-06-14-1988-07-21; WJZ-EVMAG-147-009 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 9)
    - Dan & Donna Akroyd., 1988-07-21; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 9)
    - Gilda Radner & Gene Wilder., 1988-06-14; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-22-1988-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-147-010 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 10)
    - Baltimore's Comic Commercials, Frightening Freddy, Amsterdam Unlimited., 1988-07-22; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 10)
    - Thief Of Hearts, Marla Shriver, Atlantic Shark Hunt., 1988-07-25; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-25-1988-07-29; WJZ-EVMAG-147-011 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
    - Shark Fishing., 1988-07-25; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
    - Escaping Watergate., 1988-07-26; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
    - Tank Of Gas – Annapolis., 1988-07-27; 3 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
    - Baltimore's Miracle Babies., 1988-07-28; 4 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
    - Eddie's Leading Lady., 1988-07-28; 5 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
    - Catering To The Stars., 1988-07-29; 6 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-26-1988-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-147-012 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 12)
    - Escaping Watergate, California Quakes, Dirty Dancing Disco., 1988-07-26; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 12)
    - DeNiro On The Run, Sexy Jackee, Headlock Headquarters, Tank Of Gas – Annapolis MD., 1988-07-27; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-07-28-1988-07-29; WJZ-EVMAG-147-013 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 13)
    - Tan-Talizing, Baltimore's Miracle Babies, Eddie's Leading Lady, Sharp Shades., 1988-07-28; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 13)
    - Magnum Makes History, Night Court's Brash Bailiff, Catering To The Stars., 1988-07-29; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-08-01-1988-08-05; WJZ-EVMAG-147-015 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 15)
    - Baltimore's Window Art., 1988-08-01; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 15)
    - Pin-Up Putter., 1988-08-02; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 15)
    - Far East Fantasy., 1988-08-04; 3 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 15)
    - A Man Called Cleese., 1988-08-05; 4 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-08-01-1988-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-147-016 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 16)
    - Bruce Willis, Baltimore's Window Art, America's Teen Queen., 1988-08-01; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 16)
    - Beverly Hills Bash, Pin-Up Putter, A Helping Hand., 1988-08-02; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-08-03-1988-08-04; WJZ-EVMAG-147-017 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 17)
    - Liza Bounces Back, Sex Exec, Paradise Down Under., 1988-08-03; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 17)
    - Top Spots, Far East Fantasy, Lion Around., 1988-08-04; 2 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-08; WJZ-EVMAG-147-014 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 14)
    - Fox Trot #3, 1988-08; 1 (Mixed materials 147, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1988-10-13; WJZ-EVMAG-151-001 (Mixed materials 151, Tape 1)